<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kim Tien Nguyen</title>
    <link>https://ktnvn.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kim Tien Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 18:12:33 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ktnvn.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetic Navigation System</title>
      <link>https://ktnvn.github.io/projects/mns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 18:12:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ktnvn.github.io/projects/mns/</guid>
      <description>Electromagnetic Navigation System (ENS) is one the most powerful technology to remotely manipulate and navigate the magnetic objects. These magnetic objects can be a hard magnet (permanent magnet, PM), a soft magnet (iron, nickel, etc.), or magnetic materials embedded on a tethered robots (catheters)/untethered robots (micro/nanorobots), which can be magnetically driven by exerting a magnetic torque and force on it. Let’s consider a magnetic object place inside a magnetic field (generated by the ENS), the object is firstly magnetized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ktnvn.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 12:36:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ktnvn.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>Guide-wired Helical Microrobot for Percutaneous Revascularization in Chronic Total Occlusion in-vivo Validation
Kim Tien Nguyen, Seok-Jae Kim, Hyun-Ki Min, Manh Cuong Hoang, Gwangjun Go, Byungjeon Kang, Jayoung Kim, Eunpyo Choi, Ayoung Hong, Jongoh Park, Chang-Sei Kim
IEEE Transactions on Biomedical Engineering, 2020/12/22, DOI:10.1109/TBME.2020.3046513 AbstractObjective: For the revascularization in small vessels such as coronary arteries, we present a guide-wired helical microrobot mimicking the corkscrew motion for mechanical atherectomy that enables autonomous therapeutics and minimizing the radiation exposure to clinicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About ME</title>
      <link>https://ktnvn.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 13:29:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ktnvn.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Short Biography Kim Tien Nguyen received his B.S. degree (2012) in mechanical engineering from the Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education, Vietnam, M.S. degree (2015) and Ph.D. degree (2019) in mechanical engineering from Chonnam National University, South Korea. He is now a senior researcher in Medical Microrobot center, Korea. His research interests including Micro-actuator/ Microrobot, Micro manipulation of bio-medical devices/applications.
Education Backgrounds  Mar.,2016 - Feb.,2020: Ph.D. candidate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ionic Polymer Metal Composite</title>
      <link>https://ktnvn.github.io/projects/ipmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 18:12:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ktnvn.github.io/projects/ipmc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>